hobbit-armies.com 2017-12-27

# Privacy Policy - Intelligent Demand - Real Revenue Transformation

Intelligent Demand knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

  * We don’t ask you for information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t sell or share your personal information with anyone except to provide services to you, comply with the law or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our services or to improve our prospects’ and customers’ experience on our website(s).

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Intelligent Demand collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use our website(s).

Intelligent Demand also collects potentially personally-identifying information such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. We do not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

The privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this website only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Intelligent Demand does not own or control, or to people that Intelligent Demand does not employ or manage.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Some visitors to Intelligent Demand’s websites may choose to share personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that we gather depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we may require customers who register to download information or attend an online webinar to share their name, Company name, address, phone number, company name and e-mail address. When you initially express interest obtaining additional information, or when you register for additional online events, we may also ask for additional types personal information, such as title, department name, fax number, or additional company information, such as annual revenues or marketing spend. We may also request demographic information and unique identifiers in order to provide you with a more personalized experience. Intelligent Demand does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

**Intelligent Demand will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.** Intelligent Demand discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Intelligent Demand’s behalf or to provide services available at Intelligent Demand’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Intelligent Demand’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Intelligent Demand discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Intelligent Demand, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Intelligent Demand website and have supplied your email address, Intelligent Demand may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new available information, reports, surveys, products and services, or to solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Intelligent Demand. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Intelligent Demand takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of our website(s), and their website access preferences. Intelligent Demand visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our websites, with the drawback that certain features of Intelligent Demand’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time, and in our sole discretion. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to this Privacy Policy.

### Privacy Contact Information

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

By e-mail: info@intelligentdemand.com

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
